clublaptop.com 2011-08-06

# Privacy Policy - Club Laptop

Refeel Cartridge Engineering is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to www.clublaptop.com. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us. By viewing the content of this site, registering or placing an order on this site, or contacting us by email or via this site, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy.

**Information that we collect from you**

When you visit, register or order products or services on www.clublaptop.com you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name, contact details and personal information such as your name, occupation, home and work address, telephone number, fax number, email address, printer and printer cartridge details and associated product requirements. We may also collect information about your usage of our website as well as information about you from messages you post to the website and e-mails or letters you send to us. 

**Use of your information**

Your information will enable us to provide you with access to all parts of our site and to supply the information, goods or services you have requested. We will also use and analyse the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business. In particular, we may use your information to contact you for your views on our services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the site or our services. Further, where you have consented, we might also use your information to let you know about other products and services which we offer which may be of interest to you including refilled ink cartridges, remanufactured laser cartridges, compatible cartridge, OEM cartridges, paper products, media products and accessories, computer consumables, reconditioned printers, new printers, digital photo processing and associated photography related products and services, as well as new product launches and company developments and we may contact you by post, telephone or fax, as well as by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know. 

**Disclosure of your information**

The information you provide to us will be held on our computers in the India . It may be accessed by or given to our staff working outside the India and third parties who act for us for the purposes set out in this policy or for other purposes approved by you. Those parties process information, fulfil and deliver orders, and provide support services on our behalf. We may also pass aggregate information on the usage of our site to third parties but this will not include information that can be used to identify you. Where you have consented when providing us with your details, we may also allow carefully selected third parties, including other companies in our group, to contact you occasionally about products and services which may be of interest to you including refilled ink cartridges, remanufactured laser cartridges, compatible cartridge, OEM cartridges, paper products, media products and accessories, computer consumables, reconditioned printers, new printers, digital photo processing and associated photography related products and services. They may contact you by post, telephone or fax, as well as by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted by these companies in the future, please let us know. Finally, if our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are small amounts of information which we store on your computer. Unless you have indicated your objection when disclosing your details to us, our system will issue cookies to your computer when you log on to the site. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and to personalise the content of the site for you. You may set up your computer to reject cookies although, in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our site. If you do not wish to receive cookies in the future, please let us know. For more information about cookies and how to disable or reject them, see www.aboutcookies.org.

**Changes to our privacy policy**

Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the site and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification. Contact All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to us via our published email / postal address.
